{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Home Modification Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40272/":{"taskOID":40272,"originalTaskOID":40272,"setID":575,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7254,"questionDisplayText":"Building Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of building is involved?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":202089,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Single family home","answerDisplayText":"Single family home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11441,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Condominium, apartment or town house","answerDisplayText":"Condominum, apartment or town house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202090,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Office building","answerDisplayText":"Office building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11440,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Retail store","answerDisplayText":"Retail store","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11439,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Restaurant","answerDisplayText":"Restaurant","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4435,"questionDisplayText":"Remodeling Needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What needs to be worked on? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":650,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Add ramp(s) and handrails","answerDisplayText":"Add ramp(s) and handrails","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":986,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bathroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2319,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Exterior doorway(s)","answerDisplayText":"Exterior doorway(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3321,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Interior doorway(s)","answerDisplayText":"Interior doorway(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4075,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Need suggestions","answerDisplayText":"Need suggestions","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2910,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Hallway(s)","answerDisplayText":"Hallway(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6030,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Stairways/steps","answerDisplayText":"Stairways/steps","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1457,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Closet(s)","answerDisplayText":"Closet(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200381,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Office(s)","answerDisplayText":"Office(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3594,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Lighting","answerDisplayText":"Lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2544,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Flooring","answerDisplayText":"Flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5431,"questionDisplayText":"Design Preparation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of design preparation has been done?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17474,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sketches or basic idea of project","answerDisplayText":"Sketches of basic idea of project","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9770,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Professional Drawings","answerDisplayText":"Professional Drawings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4651,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Permits pulled","answerDisplayText":"Permits pulled","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4271,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"None","answerDisplayText":"None","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7254,"questionDisplayText":"Building Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of building is involved?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":202089,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Single family home","answerDisplayText":"Single family home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11441,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Condominium, apartment or town house","answerDisplayText":"Condominum, apartment or town house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202090,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Office building","answerDisplayText":"Office building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11440,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Retail store","answerDisplayText":"Retail store","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11439,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Restaurant","answerDisplayText":"Restaurant","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":202089,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Single family home","answerDisplayText":"Single family home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11441,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Condominium, apartment or town house","answerDisplayText":"Condominum, apartment or town house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202090,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Office building","answerDisplayText":"Office building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11440,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Retail store","answerDisplayText":"Retail store","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11439,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Restaurant","answerDisplayText":"Restaurant","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4435,"questionDisplayText":"Remodeling Needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What needs to be worked on? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":650,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Add ramp(s) and handrails","answerDisplayText":"Add ramp(s) and handrails","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":986,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bathroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2319,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Exterior doorway(s)","answerDisplayText":"Exterior doorway(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3321,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Interior doorway(s)","answerDisplayText":"Interior doorway(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4075,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Need suggestions","answerDisplayText":"Need suggestions","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2910,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Hallway(s)","answerDisplayText":"Hallway(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6030,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Stairways/steps","answerDisplayText":"Stairways/steps","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1457,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Closet(s)","answerDisplayText":"Closet(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200381,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Office(s)","answerDisplayText":"Office(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3594,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Lighting","answerDisplayText":"Lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2544,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Flooring","answerDisplayText":"Flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":650,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Add ramp(s) and handrails","answerDisplayText":"Add ramp(s) and handrails","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":986,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bathroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2319,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Exterior doorway(s)","answerDisplayText":"Exterior doorway(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3321,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Interior doorway(s)","answerDisplayText":"Interior doorway(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4075,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Need suggestions","answerDisplayText":"Need suggestions","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2910,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Hallway(s)","answerDisplayText":"Hallway(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6030,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Stairways/steps","answerDisplayText":"Stairways/steps","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1457,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Closet(s)","answerDisplayText":"Closet(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200381,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Office(s)","answerDisplayText":"Office(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3594,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Lighting","answerDisplayText":"Lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2544,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Flooring","answerDisplayText":"Flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5431,"questionDisplayText":"Design Preparation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of design preparation has been done?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17474,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sketches or basic idea of project","answerDisplayText":"Sketches of basic idea of project","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9770,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Professional Drawings","answerDisplayText":"Professional Drawings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4651,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Permits pulled","answerDisplayText":"Permits pulled","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4271,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"None","answerDisplayText":"None","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":17474,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sketches or basic idea of project","answerDisplayText":"Sketches of basic idea of project","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9770,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Professional Drawings","answerDisplayText":"Professional Drawings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4651,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Permits pulled","answerDisplayText":"Permits pulled","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4271,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"None","answerDisplayText":"None","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"__cache./api/resource/task/40272/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40272,"taskName":"Remodel to Accommodate a Disability","taskDescription":"Remodel to Accommodate a Disability","xmTaskDescriptor":"Home Modification Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":294,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Remodel accessibility Accommodate Disability handicap","textMessagingName":"Remodel Disabil","rolloverLongDesc":"A properly designed space can greatly enhance the independence \u0026 safety of a person with a disability. These experts know how specific adaptations can address specific challenges. This category is for major remodeling done to accommodates the person with the disability.","rolloverShortDesc":"Substantial alterations to meet needs of disabled.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Remodel to Accommodate a Disability.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Home Modifications \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Remodeling for Disability, Accessibility \u0026 More","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":20,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Disability Remodel","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Remodel to Accommodate a Disability","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Remodeling Project","urlName":"Remodel-to-Accommodate-a-Disability","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Home Modification Companies - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Disability, Accessibility Remodeling \u0026 More","searchKeywords":"Remodel,accessibility,Accommodate,Disability,handicap,lifts,access,wheelchair,accommmodation","emcCategoryOid":-12021,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":575,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}